A Guide to the Minutes of the Faculty of the Arts and Sciences, University of Virginia, 1899-1979
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Minutes of the Faculty of the Arts and Sciences, University of Virginia 1899-1979
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-19/2/1.031
This collection consists of 26 volumes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
The collection was an archival transfer from the Office of the Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences, through Heidi Winter, on February 5, 2003.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of 26 volumes of copies of the minutes of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences.
Contents List
- Faculty Minutes 1899 Sep-1907 Jun, Vol. 1 (Box 1)
- Faculty Minutes 1907 Sep-1912 Sep, Vol. 2 (Box 1)
- Faculty Minutes 1912 Dec-1918 Dec, Vol. 3 (Box 1)
- Faculty Minutes 1919 Oct-1932 Jun, Vol. 4 (Box 2)
- Faculty Minutes 1932 Oct-1939 Nov, Vol. 5 (Box 2)
- Faculty Minutes 1940 May-1948 Jun, Vol. 6 (Box 2)
- Faculty Minutes 1948 Nov-1951 Jun, Vol. 7 (Box 3)
- Faculty Minutes 1951 Sep-1955 Jun, Vol. 8 (Box 3)
- Faculty Minutes 1955 Sep-1957 Nov, Vol. 9 (Box 3)
- Faculty Minutes 1958 Feb-1960 Jun, Vol. 10 (Box 4)
- Faculty Minutes 1960 Sep-1962 Nov, Vol. 11 (Box 4)
- Faculty Minutes 1963 Feb-1964 Nov, Vol. 12 (Box 4)
- Faculty Minutes 1965 Mar-1967 Sep, Vol. 13 (Box 5)
- Faculty Minutes 1967 Oct-1969 Sep, Vol. 14 (Box 5)
- Faculty Minutes 1969 Oct-1970 Jun, Vol. 15-16 (Box 5)
  2 volumes bound together
- Faculty Minutes 1970 Sep-1971 Jun, Vol. 17 (Box 6)
- Faculty Minutes 1971 Sep-1972 Jun, Vol. 18 (Box 6)
- Faculty Minutes 1972 Sep-1973 Jun, Vol. 19 (Box 6)
- Faculty Minutes 1973 Sep-1974 May, Vol. 20 (Box 6)
- Faculty Minutes 1974 Sep-1975 May, Vol. 21 (Box 6)
- Faculty Minutes 1975 Sep-1976 May, Vol. 22 (Box 6)
  1 bound volume - duplicate
- Faculty Minutes 1975 Sep-1976 May, Vol. 22 (Box 7)
- Faculty Minutes 1976 Sep-1977 May, Vol. 23 (Box 7)
- Faculty Minutes 1977 Sep-1978 May, Vol. 24 (Box 7)
- Faculty Minutes 1978 Sep-1979 May, Vol. 25 (Box 7)
- Faculty Minutes 1979 Sep-1980 May, Vol. 26 (Box 7)